Inventory of the Slavic Book Dealer Catalogs
Department of Special Collections
- Books Poland (Warsaw), 05.08.2000 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 1 page. Names: Malgorzata Schaefer.
- Bouchal Ltd., Dec 1999 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  Contains e-mail printouts, 4 items total. Names: Akos Dufala, James Niessen; "Bookfinder" (Hungary).
- Bowen, Joshua David - Books (San Antonio, Texas), Winter 1974 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  Contains a typewritten price list, 9 pages.
- Brill / "IDC Publishers" (Leiden, Netherlands), 1977; 1979; 1987; 1990; 2006-2007 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  Contains catalogs, price lists and related materials, 8 items total. Multilingual.
- Buchexport (Leipzig, Germany), 09.23.1974 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  Contains a catalog with numerous handwritten marks / notes. In German mostly.
- A. Buschke, Books - Serials (New York), 1956 [?] (Box 81, Folder 9)
  Contains a typewritten price list, 1 page, damaged. Multilingual.
- Cambridge University Press (New York), 2007 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  Contains a price list.
- Carnegie Endowment for International Peace (Washington, D.C.), 2007-2008 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  Contains a price list / press release.
- The Carpatho-Rusyn Research Center (State of New York), 1983 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  Contains a brochure.
- The Center for Romanian Studies (Romania - Portland, OR), 2000; 2002-2003; 2007 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  Contains two catalogs and a Web printout, 1 page.
- Central and Eastern European Online Library (Frankfurt / Main, Germany), 11.12.2008; no date (Box 81, Folder 14)
  Contains a leaflet and an e-mail printout, 1 page.
- Central European University Press (Budapest - New York), 2009; no date (Box 81, Folder 15)
  Contains a catalog and a price list.
- Chadwyck-Healey, Ltd. (Cambridge, UK), no date [1986?] (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Collets International Shop (London) [1 of ], 1981-1982; no date (Box 81, Folder 17)
  Contains catalogs, leaflets, and related materials, 23 items total. In Russian and English mostly.
- Collets International Shop (London) [2 of ], 1985-1987 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  Contains catalogs, leaflets, and related materials, 8 items total. In Russian and English mostly.
- Collets International Shop (London) [3 of ], 1989-1990; no date (Box 81, Folder 19)
  Contains catalogs, leaflets, and related materials, 24 items total (including doubles). In Russian and English mostly.
- Collets International Shop (London) [4 of 4], 1991-1993; no date (Box 81, Folder 20)
  Contains catalogs and related materials, 7 items total (including doubles). In Russian and English mostly.
- Consul-Press (Belarus), 06.10.1999 (Box 81, Folder 21)
- Cornell University Press (Ithaca, New York), 2007 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  Contains a price list / order form.
- Crayne, Janet Irene (University of Michigan), 07.22.1999 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  Contains an e-mail printout regarding Balkan news sources, 1 page.
- Cyclamen Books (Leicester, England), 01.30.2009 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 2 pages. Names: Yair Abramski.
- Diamond, Harold B., Bookseller (Burbank, California), 02.06.1978 (Box 81, Folder 25)
- Dimitri, Michael A. (Fort Wayne, Indiana), 09.18.2000 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  Contains an e-mail printout regarding new books about Macedonia, 2 pages. Names: Jean E. Dickson.
- Dobczansky, Jurij (Library of Congress), 02.18.2000 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  Contains an e-mail printout regarding "The Ukrainian Weekly" archive for 1999; 2 pages.
- Dobra Knyzhka ["A Good Book"], The Publishing House (Toronto, Canada), January 1957 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  Contains a newsletter / price list, in Ukrainian; slightly damaged.
- East View Publications, Inc. (Minneapolis, MN), 1999-2000; 2007-2008; no date (Box 81, Folder 29)
  Contains a catalog with a CD-ROM included, e-mail printouts, press releases, correspondence, 7 items total; multilingual.
- Ediciones del Hebreo Errante (Madrid), 2001-2002; no date (Box 82, Folder 1)
  Contains catalogs, leaflets, photocopies of clippings and related materials; 9 items total. Multilingual. Names: Sergei Sigei; Michael Yevzlin.
- Effect Publishing, Inc. / "Possev-U.S.A." (New York), 1985-1986; 06.01.1990 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Erudit Russian Books (Niagara Falls, New York - Toronto, Canada), no date (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Les Éditeurs Réunis (Paris) [1 of 2], 1958, 1981-1982, 1984-1986; no date (Box 82, Folder 4)
  Contains 2 photocopies, in French and Russian, 2 pages; catalogs, price lists, and related notes; 10 items total, in Russian mostly.
- Les Éditeurs Réunis (Paris) [2 of 2], 1987-1988, 1990-1991, 1993, 1995; no date (Box 82, Folder 5)
  Contains catalogs, price lists, and press releases; 10 items total, in Russian mostly.
- Fink Verlag, W. (München, Germany) / "The Magnes Press" (Jerusalem), no date (Box 82, Folder 6)
  Contains a leaflet in Russian and English. Names: "Slavica Hierosolymitana."
- Francl, H. - "Europe Printing Establishment" (Vaduz, Liechtenstein), no date (Box 82, Folder 7)
- A.Gerits and Son b.v. - Antiquarian Booksellers (Amsterdam), 1999 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- The Getty Research Institute, 07.27.2000 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 2 pages. Names: El Lissitsky; Molly Molloy; Nancy Perloff; Jennifer Wulffson; Malgorzata Schaefer.
- Glagol, The Publishing House (Saint-Petersburg), 1995 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Global View, Inc. / "Smithsonian VIDEO" (Holmes, PA), no date [1989?] (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Globus. A Slavic Bookstore (San Francisco, CA), Sept. 2004; May 2006; no date (Box 82, Folder 12)
  Contains typewritten price lists, 8 items total. In Russian.
- Greenwood Press (Westport, Conn.), Oct. 1975 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  Contains a catalog with numerous handwritten notes and marks.
- Gregg International (Brookfield, Vt.), 1990 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  Contains a press release, 1 page, and a catalog. Multilingual.
- Hammersmith Books (London), 05.03.1972 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  Contains a catalog with enclosures, heavily annotated. Multilingual.
- Harrassowitz News, 07.03.2000 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 3 pages.
- Harvard University Press" (Cumberland, RI), 2007 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  Contains a price list, 2 pages.
- Harwood Academic Publishers, 05.23.2000 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 4 pages. Names: Gerard Greenway.
- Hippocrene Books Inc. (New York), no date (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Hoffer, William, Bookseller (Vancouver, B.C.), 05.13.1982 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  Contains a catalog / price list. Names: Ferdinand A. Ossendowski.
- Hoover Institution Press (Stanford, CA), no date (Box 82, Folder 21)
  Contains a leaflet, slightly damaged.
- Hyperion Press, Inc. (Westport, CT), no date (Box 82, Folder 22)
  Contains a catalog, annotated.
- Ianeva, Snezhana (Sofia, Bulgaria), 05.11.1999 (Box 82, Folder 23)
- IDC Publishers (Leiden, The Netherlands), 1999 [?]; no date (Box 82, Folder 24)
  Contains 2 catalogs and a photocopied fragment of a catalog, 2 pages. Multilingual.
- Indiana University Press (Bloomington, IN), 2007; no date (Box 82, Folder 25)
  Contains a leaflet and a price list, 1 page.
- Institut d'Études Slaves (Paris), 1980; 1982; 1990-1993; 1999; no date (Box 82, Folder 26)
  Contains price lists / catalogs, press releases, correspondence, related materials; 20 items total. Multilingual. Names: Patricia Polansky.
- Integrum World Wide (Woodcliff Lake, NJ - Berlin), 1999-2000; no date (Box 82, Folder 27)
  Contains e-mail printouts and a business card; 6 items total. Names: Alexander Smoljanski, Elena Lebedeva.
- Interliber.com (Toronto, Canada), 05.05.2000 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 2 pages. Names: Miranda Remnek, Gordan Cucic.
- International Publishers (New York), 1998 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  Contains a book newsletter / catalog.
- Iskra Research Publishing House (Cambridge, MA), 1993 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  Contains a typewritten letter, 1 page, and a press release in Russian and English. Names: Felix Kreisel.
- Ivan Fiodorov, Joint-Stock Company (St. Petersbourg), 1994 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  Contains a leaflet. Names: Anatoly Peshkov.
- Izvestiia, The Newspaper, 10.26.1999 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- The Jagiellonian University Press (Krakow, Poland), 1992-1994 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Jauker, Hans, "Wissenschaftliches Antiquariat Buchhandlung" (Wien), no date (Box 83, Folder 7)
  Contains catalogs no. 105 and 138 with enclosures; multilingual.
- Karapetyan, Gevorg (Kiev, Ukraine), 11.29.2000 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 2 pages. Names: Malgorzata Schaefer.
- Knjizara (Belgrade, Yugoslavia), 03.01.2000 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 2 pages. Names: Sasa Drakulic.
- Kolos Corporation (Arlington, VA - Kiev, Ukraine), 08.17.2000 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 1 page. Names: Volodymyr Scherbyna, Ihor Kahanets.
- Kontakt (Vanves, France), no date (Box 83, Folder 11)
  Contains a catalog, in Polish mostly.
- Kosmas: Czech, Slovak and Central European Journal (Texas), 2000 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  Contains e-mail printouts, 2 pages total. Names: David Chroust, Clinton Machann, Layne Pierce, Dr. Mila Saskova-Pierce.
- Kovač, Anton, Dr. (München, Germany), Oct. 2000; no date (Box 83, Folder 13)
  Contains 2 catalogs with enclosures, multilingual.
- Kraus Reprint (Liechtenstein), no date (Box 83, Folder 14)
  Contains a catalog with numerous handwritten marks / notes, multilingual, and related miscellaneous materials (2 items).
- Krikorian, Serge (Begnins, Suisse), 06.27.2000; 2009; no date (Box 83, Folder 15)
  Contains 13 typewritten price lists, multilingual; a photo; a postcard; a typescript in Russian and English, 5 pages; a photocopy, 1 page; a posted envelope.
- Księgarnia SPK (London), 1974 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  Contains a catalog in Polish, slightly damaged.
- Kubon and Sagner Buchexport - Import GmbH (München, Germany), 1996; 2009 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  Contains a printed catalog in Russian and a typewritten price list, multilingual.
- Kulakov, Valery, 02.12.2009 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 1 page. Names: Aaron Goldstein.
- Lalik, Mustafa (Toronto, Canada), June 2008-June 2009; no date (Box 83, Folder 19)
  Contains a typed catalog, 37 pages, multilingual, and a typewritten letter with a handwritten signature, 1page. Names: Radovan and Barbara Matanic.
- Lexicon Maciej Wolięski (Warsaw, Poland), 1998; 2007 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  Contains a catalog, in Polish mostly, and a handwritten note, 1 page.
- Library Shop - The New York Public Library, Oct. 2007 (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Liki Rossii ["Faces of Russia"], Information-Publishing Firm (Saint-Petersburg), 1995-1996 (Box 83, Folder 22)
- Lipert Gallery (Brooklyn, NY), 1999 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  Contains a catalog in Polish and English.
- Les Livres Étrangers, S.A. (Paris), no date (Box 83, Folder 24)
  Contains a leaflet in French and English.
- A. Longo Editore (Ravenna, Italy), no date (Box 83, Folder 25)
  Contains a price list and order forms, 3 pages total, multilingual.
- Maler, Jerusalem's Russian Bookstore (Israel), no date (Box 83, Folder 26)
  Contains a typewritten annotated price list, 2 pages, in Russian mostly.
- Mezhdunarodnaia kniga ["International Book, Co."] (Moscow), 1932-1934 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  Contains catalogs and a cover of a catalog, 1 page, 8 items total (including doubles), some with occasional handwritten marks / notes and /or enclosures, some are damaged. In Russian mostly.
- MIPP International, Proficient Book Service, no date (Box 83, Folder 28)
  Contains a printed holiday postcard. Names: Karen Rondestvedt.
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 04.06.1999; Feb.-May 2000; no date (Box 83, Folder 29)
  Contains e-mail printouts, 8 items total. Names: Jolanta M. Davis, Allan Urbanic, Marianna Tax Choldin, Malgorzata Schaefer, John Schoeberlein, The Central Eurasian Studies Society, Jennie Nicolayev, Naheed Zaheer, Susan Gardos, Marianne R. Kamp, Association of Women in Slavic Studies, Zuzana Nagy.
- The MIT Press, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 30)
- Neubert, Michael, 09.09 (Box 83, Folder 31)
  1999.Contains an e-mail printout, 1 page.
- Neustein, A. and E., "Księgarnia Polska" ["The Polish Bookstore"] (Tel-Aviv, Israel), 1998-2000 (Box 83, Folder 32)
  Contains 4 catalogs / price lists, in Polish and German mostly.
- Northern Illinois University Press, 2007 (Box 83, Folder 33)
  Contains a price list / order form, 1 page.
- Georg Olms Verlag (Hildesheim, Germany - New York), no date (Box 83, Folder 34)
  Contains a catalog with an enclosure, heavily annotated, multilingual.
- One Third Publishing (Prague, Czech Republic), July-Sept. 1999 (Box 83, Folder 35)
  Contains e-mail printouts, 3 items.
- Oriental Research Partners (Newtonville, MA), 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 36)
  Contains a catalog / price list with handwritten marks / notes; multilingual. Names: Valery [Valerii] Kuharetz [Kukharets, Kulakov].
- ORPAN (Warsaw, Poland), Dec. 1988 (Box 83, Folder 37)
  Contains a catalog with numerous handwritten notes / marks, multilingual.
- The Overlook Press and Ardis Publishers, Peter Mayer Publishers, Inc. (Woodstock, NY), 2006 (Box 83, Folder 38)
  Contains a catalog, with the cover slightly damaged.
- Oxford University Press (Cary, NC), 2007 (Box 83, Folder 39)
- Panorama (Moscow), 1995 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  Contains a catalog in Russian and English.
- Parnassus Book Service (Yarmouthport, Mass.), Jan. 1974 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  Contains a catalog, multilingual, slightly damaged.
- Parry, Albert, Prof. (Cos Cob, Conn.), no date (Box 84, Folder 3)
  Contains a typewritten annotated price list, 4 pages, in English and Russian (Latin transliteration).
- Peet, Jan, "Books on Art - Periodicals - Scientific Books" (Bussum, The Netherlands), Feb. 18, 1976 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  Contains a catalog / price list with handwritten notes / marks on the cover; multilingual.
- Periodical Clearing House (Saylorsburg, Pennsylvania), Nov. 1972 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  Contains two typewritten price lists, multilingual, and a posted envelope.
- Plaza Book Auction Corp. (New York City), 1933 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  Contains a photocopy of a catalog (a fragment, 4 pages) in English and French mostly.
- Polish Scientific Publishers PWN Ltd. (Warsaw), 1994; 1997 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  Contains a catalog and a leaflet; in Polish and English.
- Poljakov, Denis (Tallinn, Estonia), 2008 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  Contains 2 e-mail printouts, 6 pages total, in Russian mostly, and photocopies of antiquarian materials (1770; 1909; no date), 7 pages, in Russian (the old orthography).
- Possev Antiquariat (Rome, Italy) - "Possev-Verlag, V.Gorachek KG." (Frankfurt am Main, Germany), 1985; 1986-1987 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  Contains 3 catalogs / price lists and related materials (book requests forms, etc.), with occasional handwritten notes / marks; multilingual. Names: N.A. Timofejeff; Alexander Timofejeff.
- Primary Source Media (Woodbridge, CT), May 1998 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  Contains 3 press releases and a business card. Names: Carol A. Ingalls.
- Princeton University Press (Princeton, NJ), 2007 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Purto, Victoria (Randolf, NJ) - "Independent Archives Rubikon" (St.Petersburg, Russia), 1992-1993; 1995 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  Contains press releases, correspondence, price lists and related materials; 7 items total; in English and Russian (both Cyrillic and Latin transliteration). Names: Igor Dashkevich.
- Quaritch, Bernard, Ltd. (London), 2008 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  Contains a catalog in English and Russian (both Cyrillic and Latin transliteration).
- Sims Reed Ltd. / "Sims Reed Rare Books" (London), 2005-2006; no date (Box 84, Folder 14)
  Contains catalogs and price lists, 5 items total. Multilingual.
- Reprint, The Publishing House (Warsaw, Poland), 1992 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Rigan (Riga, Latvia), no date [1998?] (Box 84, Folder 16)
  Contains copies of catalog entries, 7 pages, and 2 handwritten notes, attached. Names: Malgorzata Schaefer, Irina Worthug [?].
- Romanian Academy Publishing House (Romania), Nov. 15, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  Contains an e-mail printout including a price list, 18 pages total. Names: Malgorzata Schaefer, Kathy Kerns, Liviu Iancovescu.
- Norman Ross Publishing (NY), April 3, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Routledge, Taylor and Francis Group (United Kingdom), 2007; no date (Box 84, Folder 19)
  Contains catalogs, price lists / order forms, leaflets; 4 items total.
- Rowman and Littlefield Publishers, Inc. (PA), 2007 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Russian Academy of Sciences Library (Moscow), Dec. 14, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 2 pages. Names: Nadezhda Khoteeva.
- The Russian Publications Project - University of Pittsburgh (PA), March 24, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  Contains a leaflet and a press release, 1 page. In Russian and English.
- Russian Social Sciences and Humanities Network, Oct. 1, 1999 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  Contains an e-mail printout, 2 pages. Names: Jim Niessen, Dr. Irina Garshkova, Malgorzata Schaefer, Samuel H. Williamson.
- Russian Studies Publications (Medford, MA - St. Petersburg, Russia), 2005; 2007; no date (Box 84, Folder 24)
  Contains 3 catalogs / price lists, in Russian (Latin transliterations) and English, and a business card. Names: Aina B. Liubarova.
- Russica Publishers (Berlin), 2008 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  Contains 2 e-mail printouts, in Russian (Latin transliterations) and English. Names: Valery J. Cool-Kulakov.
- The Scholar's Choice (Rochester, NY), 2007 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  Contains a price list / order form, 3 pages.
- Serials, 1990s (Box 84, Folder 27)
  Contains book lists and related materials (correspondence, notes, copies of library cards, etc.), some heavily annotated. Multilingual. Notes: "Collets, The International Booksellers."
- Bernard J. Shapero, Rare Books (London) [1 of 2], 2009 (Box 84, Folder 28)
- Bernard J. Shapero, Rare Books (London) [2 of 2], 2009 (Box 84, Folder 29)
- M.E.Sharpe, Inc. (Armonk, NY), 2007 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  Contains catalogs and price lists / order forms, 4 items total.
- Shpil (Riga, Latvia), March / April 2000 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  Contains a photocopy of the "Shpil" magazine's page, in Russian.
- Sixty-Eight Publishers, Corp. (Toronto, Canada), 1986-1987 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  Contains a catalog, in Czech [and Slovak?], with handwritten marks / notes.
- Smolders, Wilhelm (Wien, Austria), no date (Box 85, Folder 4)
  Contains a catalog / price list with handwritten marks / notes on the cover. Multilingual.
- Szwede Slavic Books (Redwood City, CA), Sept. 2004; no date (Box 85, Folder 5)
  Contains a typewritten price list, in Polish and English mostly, and a e-mail printout, 1 page.
- Texas A&M University Press, no date [2007?] (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Trocchi, Mark - "Association Book Exhibit" (Alexandria, VA), 2007 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  Contains a price list / order form with an addendum, 1page.
- Ukrainian Catholic University (Washington, D.C.), Sept. 21, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  Contains a typewritten catalog / price list with numerous handwritten marks / notes, multilingual.
- University of Pittsburgh Press (PA), 2007-2008; no date (Box 85, Folder 9)
  Contains catalogs, price lists / order forms, leaflets; 5 items total.
- The University of Wisconsin Press (Madison, WI), 2007 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  Contains a price list / order form, 2 pages.
- Yale University Press (New Haven, CT), 2007; no date (Box 85, Folder 11)
  Contains press releases / price lists / order forms; 2 items.
- Zephyr Press (Somerville, Mass.), no date (Box 85, Folder 12)
  Contains two press releases.
- Addenda - "MIPP International," April 6, 2009 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  Contains an e-mail printout and a price list, 16 pages total. In English and Russian (Latin transliteration) mostly. Names: Anna L. Shparberg, Julia Knyazkova.
- Bibliomania (Oakland, CA), no date (Box 85, Folder 14)
  Contains a list no. 267, prices included.
- Sims Reed Rare Books (London, U.K.), 2009 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  Includes three items: a catalog of June, 2009, an e-mail print out with a list of books offered on the Russian & Czech avant-garde, and an illustrated catalog (188 p., n.d.): A Selection of Rare Books; prices included. Also, please see boxes: 56 and 84
- Thornton's Bookshop (Oxford, U.K.), no date (Box 85, Folder 16)
  Contains an e-mail print out with a list of books, prices included. Also, please see box 71
- Globus: a Slavic Bookstore (San Francisco, CA), 2009 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  Contains a catalog with prices: Antiquarian & Old Books 2009
- Effect: Publishing & Advertising, Inc. (Spring Valle, NY), 2008 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  Contains two catalogs: Russian Emigration Rare Books, years 1920-1975: Proza - catalog 08-2008 and Russian Wars, 20th c. - 1008-March 2008
- Saint Petersburg: Trade & Publishing (Brooklyn, NY), 2009 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  Contains a catalog: Summer 2009
- Mouton Publishers (the Hague, the Netherlands; Paris, France), 1970 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  Contains the Reprints: a catalog of 1970
- Four Continent Book Corporation (New York, NY), 1963 and 1965 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  Contains two catalogs: Russian Science: October, 1963 and Social Sciences (in Russian): February, 1965
- A. Neimanis Buchvertrieb (München, Germany), 1969-1971 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  Consists of three catalogs: Russkie knigi: Books in Russian -1969-1970, May 1970: no.1, (first supplement to the 1969-70 catalog), and 1971
- Bernard Quaritch, Ltd. (London), 2009 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  Contains one catalog: Russian Books: Recent Acquisitions, 2009/14
- Blackwell's: "B.H. Blackwell, Ltd." (Oxford, U.K.), 1960 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  Contains one catalog Russia, no. 717
- Holy Trinity Monastery: Bookstore (Jordanville, NY), 2002-2003 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  Includes two catalogs: Katalog Knizhnago magazina Sviato-Troitskago monastyra - 2003 (in Russian, illustrated) and Catalog - 2002 (English ed., also illustrated).
- Victor Kamkin, Inc., Bookstore (Washington, D.C.), 1964-1966 [1 of 2] (Box 85, Folder 26)
  Consists of six catalogs: Spetsial'nyi katalog: russkii iazyk, literaturovedenie, kritika, bibliografiia, uchebnye posobiia i dr. - 1964, Katalog: beletristika (romany, povesti, rasskazy) - 1964, Katalog: istoriia, pravo, voennoe delo, vospominaniia - 1964, Katalog: filologiia, prosveshchenie - 1966, Katalog: slovari, entsiklopedii - 1966
- Victor Kamkin, Inc., Bookstore (Washington, D.C.), 1970-1971 [2 of 2] (Box 85, Folder 27)
  Consists of seven catalogs: Katalog: filologiia, prosveshchenie - 1970, Katalog: filologiia, prosveshchenie: vypusk 2 (I-P) - 1970, Katalog: filologiia, prosveshchenie: vypusk 3 (R-Ia) - 1970, Katalog: istoriia, pravo, vospominaniia, voennoe delo, politika: vypusk 1: (A-I) - 1971, Katalog: istoriia, pravo, vospominaniia, voennoe delo, politika: vyp. 2 (K-P), nos. 1098-2219 - 1971, Katalog: istoriia, pravo, vospominaniia, voennoe delo, politika: vyp. 3 (R-Ia), nos. 2220-3236 - 1971, and Katalog: filosofia, religiia, psikhologia, logika - 1971
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), 1988-1999 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  Consists of 12 soft bound catalogs: 1988, no. 138: Serbo-Croatian Books; 1989/1990, no. 175: Books in Belarussian and about Belarussia; 1990/1991, no. 172: Catalogue of books in Slovak; 1990/1992, no. 173: Ukrainian catalogue; 1994, no. 216: Books in Czech: Katalog Ceskych Knih; 1995, no. 201: Polish antiquarian, out-of-print & short supply titles; 1995, no. 221: Books in Polish: Plays and Poetry: recent arrivals and from stock; Autumn 1995, no. 223: Books in Bulgarian; 1995 Autumn, no. 222: Books in Czech: Katalog Ceskych Knih; 1997, no. 232: Books in Czech: Catalogue Ceskyh Knih; Autumn 1998, no. 242: Catalogue of Polish Judaica; Winter 1999, no. 245: Books in Polish: Polish Publications in Exile from 1940s until mid 1990.
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), 2000. (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), 2001 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Catalogs: "Szwede Slavic Bookstore" (Palo Alto, CA), 2002 (Box 86, Folder 4)